https://www.jacksonkelly.com/info/disclaimer-privacy-policy

The Jackson Kelly PLLC Disclaimer
The materials included in this World Wide Web site have been prepared by Jackson Kelly PLLC for informational purposes only and are not legal advice. This information is not intended to create, and receipt of it does not constitute, a lawyer-client relationship. Internet subscribers and online readers should not act upon this information without seeking professional counsel. Do not send us information until you speak with one of our lawyers and get direction as to what information may be appropriate. This is required because we cannot represent you until we have determined that doing so would not cause a conflict of interest and we have a mutually acceptable written representation agreement with you. If your jurisdiction requires us to designate a principal office and/or a single attorney as responsible for this World Wide Web site, Jackson Kelly PLLC designates its office in Charleston, West Virginia, USA as its principal office and designates Ellen S. Cappellanti, CEO, as the responsible attorney. The rules of some jurisdictions require us to state: THIS IS AN ADVERTISEMENT.
About Jackson Kelly PLLC
Jackson Kelly PLLC is a professional limited liability company, which, together with predecessor general partnerships, has practiced law since 1822.
No Guarantee of Results
Some of the case summaries, reports of past results and individual lawyer biographies on this website describe past matters handled for clients of the Firm. These descriptions are meant only to provide information to the public about the activities and experience of our lawyers. They are not intended as a guarantee that the same or similar results can be obtained in every matter undertaken by our lawyers. You must not assume that a similar result can be obtained in a legal matter of interest to you. The outcome of a particular matter can depend on a variety of factors—including the specific factual and legal circumstances, the ability of opposing counsel, and, often, unexpected developments beyond the control of any client or lawyer.
Privacy of Client Information
Every lawyer and employee of Jackson Kelly PLLC is required by the Code of Professional Responsibility of his or her state to keep all matters related to the business of our clients and customers confidential. This confidentiality requirement extends to all personnel and precludes discussion of a client's business with persons other than those with a need to know who are actively working for the Firm or who are duly authorized representatives of the client. In addition to the professional requirements of confidentiality, the Firm has a strict policy on confidentiality of client information. We value the trust and confidence which our clients place in us.
Privacy Policy Notice
This Privacy Policy Notice tells you the kind of information we collect about you, with whom we share it and how we protect it responsibly. The notice applies to clients who obtain financial products or services for personal, family or household purposes. The examples you find in this notice are for purposes of illustration only and should not be considered to be a complete description of our information practices.
Categories of Information Which We Collect
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you with respect to our representation, from applications for loans with third parties or from other forms;
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others; and
Information which we receive from third parties as a result of our representation, including persons providing services in connection with your transactions.
Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
We do not disclose information about you to third parties except as required or permitted by law, specifically authorized by you or required under the Rules of Professional Conduct applicable to the lawyers in our Firm. If your relationship with us terminates or becomes inactive, we will continue to treat the information we have collected about you as confidential, in accordance with this Notice.
Our Security Procedures
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect client information. Our employees are bound by laws and our policies which limit their access to client information to access for legitimate purposes only and which require them to keep information about clients confidential.
Other Privacy Protections
You may have other privacy protections under some state or federal laws. We will comply with all applicable state and federal laws as to information about you.
Our Commitment
We will continue to maintain our dedication to protecting your privacy. If you have questions concerning this Notice, please call us at (304) 340-1000 between the hours of 9:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m. weekdays or visit our web site at www.jacksonkelly.com.
Overview
The Jackson Kelly PLLC Disclaimer
The materials included in this World Wide Web site have been prepared by Jackson Kelly PLLC for informational purposes only and are not legal advice. This information is not intended to create, and receipt of it does not constitute, a lawyer-client relationship. Internet subscribers and online readers should not act upon this information without seeking professional counsel. Do not send us information until you speak with one of our lawyers and get direction as to what information may be appropriate. This is required because we cannot represent you until we have determined that doing so would not cause a conflict of interest and we have a mutually acceptable written representation agreement with you. If your jurisdiction requires us to designate a principal office and/or a single attorney as responsible for this World Wide Web site, Jackson Kelly PLLC designates its office in Charleston, West Virginia, USA as its principal office and designates Ellen S. Cappellanti, CEO, as the responsible attorney. The rules of some jurisdictions require us to state: THIS IS AN ADVERTISEMENT.
About Jackson Kelly PLLC
Jackson Kelly PLLC is a professional limited liability company, which, together with predecessor general partnerships, has practiced law since 1822.
No Guarantee of Results
Some of the case summaries, reports of past results and individual lawyer biographies on this website describe past matters handled for clients of the Firm. These descriptions are meant only to provide information to the public about the activities and experience of our lawyers. They are not intended as a guarantee that the same or similar results can be obtained in every matter undertaken by our lawyers. You must not assume that a similar result can be obtained in a legal matter of interest to you. The outcome of a particular matter can depend on a variety of factors—including the specific factual and legal circumstances, the ability of opposing counsel, and, often, unexpected developments beyond the control of any client or lawyer.
Privacy of Client Information
Every lawyer and employee of Jackson Kelly PLLC is required by the Code of Professional Responsibility of his or her state to keep all matters related to the business of our clients and customers confidential. This confidentiality requirement extends to all personnel and precludes discussion of a client's business with persons other than those with a need to know who are actively working for the Firm or who are duly authorized representatives of the client. In addition to the professional requirements of confidentiality, the Firm has a strict policy on confidentiality of client information. We value the trust and confidence which our clients place in us.
Privacy Policy Notice
This Privacy Policy Notice tells you the kind of information we collect about you, with whom we share it and how we protect it responsibly. The notice applies to clients who obtain financial products or services for personal, family or household purposes. The examples you find in this notice are for purposes of illustration only and should not be considered to be a complete description of our information practices.
Categories of Information Which We Collect
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you with respect to our representation, from applications for loans with third parties or from other forms;
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others; and
Information which we receive from third parties as a result of our representation, including persons providing services in connection with your transactions.
Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
We do not disclose information about you to third parties except as required or permitted by law, specifically authorized by you or required under the Rules of Professional Conduct applicable to the lawyers in our Firm. If your relationship with us terminates or becomes inactive, we will continue to treat the information we have collected about you as confidential, in accordance with this Notice.
Our Security Procedures
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect client information. Our employees are bound by laws and our policies which limit their access to client information to access for legitimate purposes only and which require them to keep information about clients confidential.
Other Privacy Protections
You may have other privacy protections under some state or federal laws. We will comply with all applicable state and federal laws as to information about you.
Our Commitment
We will continue to maintain our dedication to protecting your privacy. If you have questions concerning this Notice, please call us at (304) 340-1000 between the hours of 9:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m. weekdays or visit our web site at www.jacksonkelly.com.
Site Map
Privacy Policy/Disclaimer
Careers
Ancillaries
Remote Access
